( wind whooshing )
( heavy breathing )
- ( growling ) - ( gasps )
( crying )
- ( louder growling ) - ( shrieks )
( grunts )
( screams )
Enid : Hang on .
( tape rewinds )
( woman whimpering on TV )
( screams )
( door opens )
( footsteps )
Not still going over it ?
Well , if we 're passing it as an 18 , it needs more cuts .
The decapitation ?
Nope . No , the decapitation is ridiculous .
It 's the , er , it 's the eye gouging ...
it 's too , it 's too realistic .
Plus , I was trying to see who dragged her away .
Sanderson : Does it matter ?
Well , would be nice if it has some clear retribution after all the ...
I appreciate you analyzing this with such precision , Enid ,
but perhaps someone got out of the cautious side
of bed this morning ?
Well , I 'm just doing my job .
Sanderson : You 're missing the intellectual layer ,
- my dear . - Oh , come on , we both saw how ...
The heightened references take the edge off
the more realistic violence .
See it less as an eye gouging , more part of a grand tradition .
It 's no worse than the Cyclops in Homer .
It 's Gloucester in Lear .
It 's ... Un Chien Andalou .
I 've salvaged the tug of war with the intestines .
I 've kept in most of the screwdriver stuff .
And I 've only trimmed the tiniest bit
off the end of the genitals .
But some things should be left to the imagination .
It 's like Rat Brothel all over again .
No , I just want to get it right .
Plus , you lost the argument the moment you brought
Shakespeare into the room .
( sighs )
We can 't afford to make mistakes .
I 'm cutting it .
News presenter : As Britain is invaded by a wave of depraved
and corrupt horror videos ,
prosecutions of distributors of the video nasties ...
Reporter 1 : What we 're talking about are videos that depict
butchering , sadism , murder .
This is dangerous and hardcore stuff .
News presenter : And Britain 's rising crime
with one conservative MP
stating that these violent films
are gnawing at society 's moral fabric .
Reporter 2 : Violence is an inherent part of human nature
and it 's important that we find
a cathartic outlet for this
otherwise , it remains pent up , uncontrolled .
Reporter 3 : I even heard from one social worker ,
who at 5.30 in the morning visiting a family ,
he wasn 't allowed to start his visit
until the rape scene
from I Spit On Your Grave had been finished ...
Reporter 4 : Far too many violent images ,
which are penetrating the minds
of impressionable young children .
Reporter 5 : There 's a real danger
of confusing fiction with reality .
News presenter : The raids up and down the country ,
Trading Standards have seized over four thousand films
from video shops
as well as from private homes .
Mary : If this film stays
in your mind ...
its presence is corrupting .
Reporter 6 : These increasingly sadistic
and violent films are being watched
and rewatched over and over again .
Viewers are like drug addicts
wanting stronger and harder films every time .
Reporter 7 : There 's clear evidence
that these films are lowering standards in society .
And we should be afraid what else they might do to people ...
News presenter 2 : With more video recorders per person
than any other country in the world ,
Britain is the leader of the video revolution .
- ( creature growls ) - ( woman screams )
( dramatic music playing )
( muffled whimpering from TV )
( man sobs )
( screams )
Enid : This depiction is dangerous .
Come on , Enid . No one 's gonna pick this up
and think it 's a documentary . It 's so fake .
To you it might be sausages for intestines ,
- but what if it gets into the hands of children ? - Exactly !
Kids could be rewinding and watching those scenes
over and over again .
Which is exactly what new government guidelines
are pointing at .
- Video technology is changing the rules ... - More guidelines . Great .
Not as if we haven 't got enough on our hands .
Sanderson : How can we do our job properly
if we 're constantly bogged down by government bureaucracy ?
If it 's the nation 's sanity they 're worried about ,
why don 't they stop slashing
- social services ? - Fraser : Okay , I get it .
But I 'm afraid we 're not here to debate the government .
Can we get back on track , please ?
Consensus on Cannibal Carnage ?
- Reject . - I agree .
A few cuts .
I 'd pass it .
Enid .
( screams loudly )
So , we 're both recommending reject ?
Yes .
Can I be a massive pain and get you to type up my notes ?
Of course . No problem , Anne .
Anne : It 's my sister 's birthday .
I should have been there half an hour ago .
Are you sure that 's okay ?
You should go .
Anne : Thanks , Enid .
See you tomorrow .
( distant screams )
( typewriter keys clicking )
( woman 's laughter echoes )
Woman 1 : I can 't believe you did , though .
- You are nuts . - Woman 2 : Oh my God !
- Woman 1 : Love you so much . - Woman 2 : Oh , I love you more .
( both giggling )
Excuse me !
Sorry , excuse me !
Er , sorry , I thought you were someone else .
( clamoring )
Margaret Thatcher : What we have seen in this country
is the emergence of an organized
revolutionary minority ,
who are prepared to exploit industrial disputes
but whose real aim
is the breakdown of law and order
and the destruction of democratic
parliamentary government .
( crowd applauding on TV )
News presenter : The gas industry 's main unions
have today announced
that they will delay their decision
regarding any industrial action to assist the miners ...
( inhales )
( phone rings )
... were set to take place later this week ,
which have now been postponed indefinitely .
( phone continues ringing )
Enid : ( over answering machine ) This is Enid Baines .
Please leave a message .
( beep )
June : ( over speaker ) Hi Enid . It 's Mom .
Oh , I don 't like talking to these things .
Well , if you 're there , Dad and I booked the table
for 9 p.m.
It 's at the restaurant that Dad mentioned .
Er , see you there , love . Bye .
( beep fading away )
( quiet indistinct chatter )
The food here is meant to be good .
Mm .
This is a death certificate .
Waitress : Ready to order ?
Maybe we need another minute .
Have they found something ?
No , Enid .
We just felt ...
What 's going on ?
Your Dad and I have been thinking about this
for a long time .
It hasn 't been an easy decision .
Enid , I know it 's difficult ,
but we need to find a way to let go .
Let go ?
June : Try to find some sort of peace ?
Your Dad and I aren 't going to be around forever
and I don 't want to grow old wishing
for a happy ending
that we all know might never come .
So , are you deciding that she 's dead ?
But this marks her death as that day .
I was there . I would know if she died .
You 've never been clear on exactly what you remember .
I can try and remember , Mom . Is that what you want me to do ?
- I can , you know ... - Enid , we 've done that .
That 's the point .
We 'll never know what happened .
Yeah , so she 's still missing .
Enid , if we were going to ...
we should have found her by now .
You know if someone did take her , then ...
then they 're still out there .
Enid .
Sorry .
We 're not blaming you .
Mom and I are only trying to do what 's best , love .
June : It 's the right decision for all of us , Enid .
Please ?
No , that 's a copy for you to keep .
- ( inhales anxiously ) - George : Patrick recommended
the fish .
Viv said they had a lovely time here .
- Mm . - ( chuckles )
So , how 's work , Enid ?
Seen anything you 'd recommend ?
It 's not entertainment , Mom .
I do it to protect people .
June : Yes , of course . Well ,
let 's all just try to have a lovely meal .
Shall we ?
( thunder rumbles )
( inhales )
( sighs )
( muffled noise )
- Woman : It 's always the same with you . - Man : What ?
Woman : You know , taking no responsibility .
Man : I never take responsibility ?
What , you lose your fucking job
and I 'm the one that doesn 't take responsibility ?
( quietly ) I 've had enough of this shit !
Man : Fucking kid to feed .
Woman : ( quietly ) Don 't be bringing him into it .
Man : It 's fucking typical .
( inhales deeply )
Late night ?
One too many white wines .
Well , let 's hope there 's nothing too stomach churning coming up then .
What masterpiece are we dissecting ?
Extreme Coda .
( Anne chuckles )
( tape starts playing )
( grunting )
( woman whimpers )
- ( woman screams ) - ( man grunts )
( struggle continues )
- ( man moans ) - ( rhythmic thumping )
( woman continues screaming )
Anne : I mean , what is it with these directors ?
Male inadequacy revenge catharsis .
Didn 't that get to you ?
Some of those scenes were so excessive .
Just focus on getting it right .
Don 't really think about anything else .
Plus , I haven 't got a hangover .
( Anne chuckles )
Enid , Fraser wants to see us . Says it 's urgent .
Fraser : Shut the door .
You two passed Deranged , right ?
- Deranged ? - Yes . The Moreno film .
We watched it a few months ago . Why ?
There 's a , a sequence in it where a man eats someone 's face .
- Oh , yes . - Yes . 18 with extensive cuts .
What 's happened , Fraser ?
A man that was arrested in Brighouse yesterday .
He , er ...
killed his wife , then he , ...
then he tore off and ate her face .
W ... went on to shoot his two children , dead .
It 's horrific .
I got a call from some
journalist 15 minutes ago who was breaking the story .
He 's linking the killings directly to Deranged .
Oh God ! So , they 're blaming us ?
Well , there 's the thing .
This journalist seemed to know that it was you two
who passed the film .
How the hell do they know that ?
I can 't believe you two let it get past you .
It 's complete hysteria .
It 's no worse than other material we 've passed .
Fraser : The press are going to town
calling him the ' Amnesiac Killer ' .
He 's saying he can 't remember what happened .
Government policy 's already breathing down
our necks without this .
It 's a complete disaster .
I mean , I can 't believe you 'd go off
like that without permission , either of you ... ( voice fades )
( chimes )
Man : ( muffled ) Why did you leave her in the forest ?
Fraser : Enid , how ?
Sorry .
I 'm so sorry .
I need you to walk me through your decisions again .
So , I 'm 100 % clear .
And for the record , in future ,
if you have even the slightest doubt ...
just reject the film .
News reader : The man , who went berserk
claims he cannot recall the incident at all .
The accused has been dubbed by press
as ' The Amnesiac Killer '
after links being made today between the killing
and video nasty horror film , Deranged .
Neighbor : ( over TV ) I heard the most awful scream .
Made my blood go cold .
And now they 're saying it 's because of some film .
Looks like the world 's gone mad .
This has always been a really safe neighborhood ,
- like , for the kids and that . For everyone ... - ( phone rings )
News reader : A hotel in Painswick has been cleared
of staff and guests
after police found what could be a bomb
hidden in one of the hotel 's rooms .
- Mom ? - Caller : Despicable woman .
Letting people see that disgusting film ,
you should be ashamed of yourself .
( phone rings )
( muffled sobbing )
George : Enid !
Where is she ?
Enid !
June : ( crying ) No ! No !
Man : Oi , watch it , mate !
- Journalist 1 : Miss Baines ! - Journalist 2 : Enid ,
why did you allow Deranged to be released ?
Journalist 3 : Do you feel you have blood on your hands ?
Journalist 2 : Is the Amnesiac Killer telling the truth ?
Journalist 4 : Why aren 't you banning these films ?
( keys clicking )
- ( knock on door ) - Fraser : Come in .
Doug : Fraser , you sly old bastard .
Fraser : Doug , hi . Come in .
( paper rustles )
( indistinct chatter )
Sanderson : ( muffled ) I mean , my kids are reading this .
How the fuck do they know who passed it ?
- You think she blabbed to the press ? - Gordon : Oh , yeah .
Sanderson : It 's not even like we 're paid that much .
I could go to academia like that . ( snaps fingers )
Seriously . And that , that scene is laughable !
Even Little-Miss-Perfect thought it was funny .
( Gordon laughs )
Enid .
Bad luck , isn 't it ?
I mean , it could have happened to any of us .
If I 'm here to make decisions it can 't be ' bad luck ' .
Gordon : No . But , well ,
you know what I mean .
We all make mistakes .
Young Enid : Nina , spin .
One , two , three .
( Doug laughs )
That 's a single malt now , Fraser .
- Don 't be using that to drown your sorrows . - Er , yeah .
( laughs )
And who 's this you 've got squirreled away ?
Er , this is Enid Baines . She 's one of our censors .
So , this is Enid .
- Have we met ? - No .
Doug Smart . Producer , Ident Investment Films .
Fraser , you didn 't tell me you had such a photogenic team .
Now tell me this Enid , if you get bored
of banning my films ,
I 'm sure I could get you a job on the big screen .
I 'm not sure how much I like the idea of being raped
and cut into pieces on camera .
( chuckles )
No , but I 'm sure the public would love it .
Fraser : Okay , Doug , come on .
Maybe Enid could , er ,
watch my latest Frederick North submission ?
It 's from the archives . It 's harmless , I promise .
I , er ... I 'm sure you could slip me a 15 .
Fraser : It 's , er , already on her schedule .
And I 'm sure she 'll deal with it
with her usual professionalism .
Right , come on , Doug . Let me see you out .
Enchante , mademoiselle .
What a wee cracker she is . Absolutely gorgeous .
( typewriters clicking )
There were so many shits and fucks ,
it was impossible to cut them all ,
so we just had to give it a 15 .
Anyway ...
- Thank you , Alf . - Alf : All right .
What have we got now then ? ( sighs )
Don 't Go In The Church .
There won 't be many places left for us to go soon .
( laughs )
Frederick North film .
Haven 't seen one of his in a while .
Used to be quite prolific .
Don 't think I know his work .
Oh , he 's a laugh a minute .
Oh , silent titles .
Unusual .
Girl 1 : This way .
Girl 2 : Please stop .
I don 't like it . Can we go back ?
Girl 1 : No , it 'll be fun .
Let 's play a game .
( inaudible whispering )
Come on .
Summon my shadow .
Spin .
( clears throat )
Girl 1 : Do it !
One ...
Two ...
Three ...
Go on .
In there .
Go !
( breathes anxiously )
( chimes )
( inhales )
( wood creaks )
( screams )
( loud thud of chopping )
( squelching )
( chopping continues )
- ( grunts ) - ( squelching )
( gasps )
( inhales sharply )
( growls )
( breathes heavily )
( coughs )
Perkins : You okay ?
It was quite full on .
It shook me up .
Just feeling a bit under the weather .
You know you can always talk to me , don 't you ?
If you want to .
Stressful times .
Like when my mom passed away ,
if I hadn 't had someone to talk to
I think I might of just ...
I don 't know ,
- lost it ... - Why do you think he can 't remember ?
Er , who ?
The Amnesiac Killer .
Oh , I ... I don 't know .
I mean , why wouldn 't he remember ?
God , it 's hard to ...
Could be basic trauma .
Brain sort of shuts it out .
Could have had a bang on the head even . Or ...
It makes me think of my psychotherapy days
we 'd talk about how people construct
stories to cope .
You 'd be surprised what the human brain
can edit out when it can 't handle the truth .
Look .
You 're good at your job , Enid .
Don 't let what 's going on out there get to you .
I don 't know if you want to but maybe we could get out
of here sometime ?
Go for a drink .
I 'm so sorry about your mom , Perkins .
Thank you for this .
( footsteps echoes )
( distant sobbing )
Hello ?
( whimper )
( footsteps )
June : ( over phone ) Hello ?
Enid : Hi , Mom .
June : Oh , Enid . Are you okay ?
I 've been trying to get hold of you .
Sorry . Work 's been ...
really busy .
June : Oh , okay .
Well , I hope you 're all right , love .
Are you still there , love ?
Yes .
It 's , um ...
I examined this film today .
June : Oh . What was it about ?
Nothing .
It doesn 't matter .
June : You ... you mustn 't let work get you down , Enid .
I saw the news .
- It 's only ' cause your Dad ... - Dad doesn 't know
what he 's talking about .
- June : All right , love . - I 'm sorry .
Just tired .
June : Well , don 't overdo it , will you ?
You can 't be responsible for everyone , Enid .
It 's just a job .
Yeah . I suppose so .
( TV playing in the distance )
- ( beep ) - ( static )
( static continues )
( heavy breathing )
( ominous music playing )
( static continues )
( chimes )
Nina ?
( wind whistles )
( growling )
( tense music playing )
( moaning and crying )
Mom ?
It 's all your fault !
( upbeat cartoon music over TV )
( creaking )
( meows )
( sighs )
( muffled whimpers )
Valerie .
Hang on .
( typing )
What is it ?
Um , Perkins and I examined
Don 't Go In The Church yesterday .
Well , the file 's a bit thin on information .
I was wondering if you had anything else
on the director .
It 's Frederick North .
Do you have a list of his films ?
No .
Well , without a list , it 'll take at least a week .
Leaving on time , Enid ? It 's not like you .
( ominous music playing )
Boy : Beastman 's coming to get you !
( laughs )
( shop bell rings )
Gerald : Oh , hi .
Er , enjoy it ?
Customer : Yeah , proper gory .
Gerald : It 's good , isn 't it ? See you next time .
Customer : Cheers , Gerald .
( shop bell rings )
- Gerald : Hey . - I thought that one was banned .
Um , I don 't know what you mean .
Maybe you can help me ? I was looking for
some of the more unusual
Frederick North films ?
I 've seen , um ...
Don 't Go In The Church .
Oh .
Perhaps maybe you might have something else of his
under the counter .
Um ... I 've not seen you in here before .
Just moved to the area .
Someone like you doesn 't want to watch films like that .
Like what ?
My favorite is , er , Stationery Massacre .
The repeated stabbing of the man 's eye with a compass
then his stomach being ripped open
- with serrated scissors . - ( exhales )
His guts falling out , his , his stomach
being stapled back together .
( exhales )
Masterpiece .
All right , come on . I 've seen , I 've seen
that you 've got Cannibal Carnage .
And I know that that 's been banned .
Bloody hell .
Okay .
So many places getting , you know , shut down .
Police raids and ...
My mate up town had his lot confiscated .
( distant sirens )
Gerald : Honestly , it 's not worth the bloody stress .
Gonna get rid of it all soon myself anyway . So ...
That 's all I 've got of North 's .
It 's a bit of a ropey copy .
Might be a bit fuzzy in all the good bits .
And , er , well , someone 's taped over the end
with another film .
( cassette player clicks )
Alice : This place gives me a bad feeling .
It 's like something from one of my nightmares .
Let 's go back .
Tom : No , we 've come too far to turn back .
Woman : Strange .
- Tom : What is it ? - Alice : A book .
There 's a symbol .
It 's like some sort of portal .
Wait , let me see .
It 's Latin .
I can work it out .
" Si introibunt
hoc sepulcrum , dare
tibi ad infernum ... "
Tom . Stop !
It could be dangerous .
" Qui este cunum quam reverterto . "
" Quis hog momento insemperternum . "
" Imutata sinsintuar . "
He 's calling for me .
( tape whirrs )
Tom : " Sinsintuar . "
Alice : He 's calling for me .
The evil is contagious .
( tape whirrs )
Alice : He 's calling for me .
The evil is contagious .
( ominous music playing )
( tape whirrs )
( Alice screaming )
( TV clicks off )
( breathes deeply )
June : We definitely had some Jaffa cakes .
Sorry , I should have phoned .
( tuts ) Oh , where do things end up ?
I should have got more bits in .
Do you remember Carol and Alan , Enid ?
Hm .
Alan , with the squinty eye .
They broke up .
Such a shame .
Carol 's moving near the seaside now .
I suppose she 's better off out of it
but I 'm going to miss her .
You can visit , love .
I wanted to talk to you about something .
- Found a nice fella ? - No .
It 's to do with Nina .
I know what we talked about and I understand ,
but think I ...
I think I might have worked out where she is .
George : Oh , please , Enid . Not this again .
Enid : I know , Dad , but this is different .
There 's this actress .
Her name is Alice Lee .
I know it sounds mad , but I 've got this ...
( exhales ) I 've got this really strong feeling
that I think it 's her .
I need you to look at this . Just focus on her face .
Just look at her eyes .
George : We 've been here before , Enid . Every time it 's not her .
Dad , please ! You 're not even looking at her .
Please ! Just look .
She looks just like the police mock-up , Dad .
June : Enid , stop !
- Dad . - June : Enid .
George : This is exactly why we did what we did .
We tried to do our best for you ,
but you go off doing whatever you want .
Just like the day you went off with her !
George !
( static noise )
( ominous music playing )
( breathes deeply )
( haunting music playing )
( breathes heavily )
( growling )
( pants )
No , Nina !
( echoing ) No !
( ominous music plays )
( ominous music continues )
( door creaks and opens )
( tense music building )
( doorbell rings )
Doug .
I was in the area .
We met at the censor 's office .
Of course . Enid .
Um ...
Sorry , I 've been having a bit of bother .
Um , some people don 't seem to like my films .
Do come in .
Through here .
( rain pattering )
Do you live alone ?
Yes . I live alone .
This room seems familiar .
Doug : Must be a sign .
( pouring drink )
It 's the rape scene from Extreme Coda .
( glasses clinking )
Doug : Someone 's got a keen eye .
I got this for Coda in LA .
Go to the States quite a bit actually .
We look similar , don 't we ?
Who ?
Me and Alice Lee .
You do actually .
I knew you reminded me of someone .
Why don 't we get this wet coat off ?
What 's Frederick like ?
What can I say ?
He 's a provocateur and a genius .
He 's widely misunderstood .
You enjoyed Don 't Go In The Church then , huh ?
Frederick pressed for you to view it .
Wanted a woman 's eye on his film .
You not enjoying your scotch ?
You might be interested to hear that he 's shooting
a juicy sequel to Church at the moment ,
with the monstrous ' Beastman ' .
Sequels are all the rage these days .
Where are they filming it ?
Near Frederick 's .
In the forest where we shot the original .
And Alice Lee 's in it ?
It 'll be her last film .
She 's come to the end of her shelf life , that one .
W ... what does that mean ?
( groans ) Let 's not talk about some silly actress .
Far more interested in talking about you , Enid .
What 's going to happen to Alice ?
Well , that 's top secret .
Frederick abducted her , didn 't he ?
I can abduct you if you want .
- Stop ! Get off me . - What ?
- Came round my house . - Let go of me .
- You fucking prick tease . - Just let go of me , please !
- Stop . - Get ...
Stop ! Please stop !
- ( grunting ) - Enid : Just let go of me !
( Doug gurgles )
( shivers )
( gasps and gurgles )
- ( inhales deeply ) - ( shoulder cracks )
Thank you for the whiskey .
I 'll see myself out .
( breathes deeply )
( phone rings )
Caller : You fucking sick bitch .
I hope you get what 's coming to you .
You deserve to get sliced up , you fucking prick tease .
People like you shouldn 't be
given any bloody responsibility .
The evil is contagious
and it 's all your fault , you horrible woman .
You came round my fucking house .
He 's shooting a juicy sequel to Church at the moment .
You 're rotten inside .
Nothing you ever do will be any good .
You touch things , and they go to shit .
( voice becomes indistinct )
( distant screams )
( whispers echo )
Help me , please .
Please , please .
( voices and whispering stop )
( film playing over TV )
Enid ?
Anne : You all right ?
- ( growls ) - ( screams )
We are in a viewing here .
Alice Lee : Help me , help me . Save me , please !
Sanderson : Er , Enid ?
Sorry .
Someone 's losing the plot .
( scream echoes )
Hello ? Can I help you ?
Excuse me , Enid !
What do you think you 're doing ?
Everything is under control , Valerie .
All right ?
No ! No , no , no ! You 're not authorized !
Anne : " The Amnesiac Killer stated in court
that he had never seen the film Deranged ,
which is supposed to have influenced
- the attack on ... " - What ?
So , he didn 't even watch it ?
That 's what it says here .
( clamoring )
Get back !
( clamoring continues )
- ( clamor grows distant ) - ( static )
( inaudible )
( ominous music playing )
( distant screams )
( screams )
Is this the film shoot with Alice Lee ?
You 're late .
Sorry ?
I 'm Debbie . I 'll be doing your make-up .
You don 't look anything like your picture .
At least you 're here . Half the cast haven 't turned up .
Production 's all over the place .
Come on .
Let 's get you ready .
Debbie : Top off .
Head through .
Sit .
Down on the chair .
( knocks on door )
Frank : Debbie !
Is that the sister ?
Yeah .
Frank : Frederick wants her down in the forest .
He 's getting impatient .
Oh , also still no sign of the producer .
It 's so weird .
Mm ?
Doug never misses a gory murder scene .
( ominous music playing )
What have they got planned for Alice Lee ?
What do you mean ?
Look at me .
( camera clicks )
( haunting music playing )
( animal cry )
Frederick : I 've been waiting for you .
Fred ... Frederick North ?
Frederick : Step into the light , so I can see you .
Hurry up .
Where 's Alice Lee ?
Frederick : Big fan , are you ?
Well , someone told me this was her last picture .
You 're guarded .
That comes from a place of fear , doesn 't it ?
I want you to tell me about Don 't Go In The Church .
That ...
That bit with the girls where did the ...
where did the idea come from ?
Frederick : Had an effect on you , did it ?
( sniffs )
That scene ...
was inspired
by a true story .
( reel whirring )
Frederick : All of my ideas ...
are drawn from real life .
Well , that 's not what happened .
Frederick : People think that I create ...
the horror ,
but I don 't .
Horror is already out there ...
in all of us .
It 's in you .
No , it 's not .
Frederick : Of course , it is .
( chuckles ) Don 't be so naïve .
If you 're gonna do this ,
I will need you to access
your darkest impulses .
I don 't have any .
Frederick : No , they 're in there . Somewhere .
- No , they 're not . - Oh , come on !
Fucking commit !
Improvise .
Take control of your story .
No .
Okay , piss off then !
No , please , no ! Wait , wait ! Please , please . Wait .
I just want my sister .
I just want to see her ! I just really want to see
my little sister . I want her back , please !
Please !
Frederick : All right .
All right , we 'll go with that .
Let 's play .
There 's something rotten inside you .
You try to control it ,
but you only make things worse .
Don 't fight it anymore .
- Stop . - Just let it out !
Stop , it 's you .
You 're trying to make me out to be the bad person
and it 's you . Stop !
There . That 's it .
And we 'll take that energy
into the scene .
Come ...
enter your story .
- ( reel whirring ) - ( heavy breathing )
( loud whirring )
( ominous music playing )
( gasps )
( chimes )
Beastman : My love .
I have been waiting for you .
For such a long time .
You have always been in my heart .
( tense music playing )
( chain rattles )
Enid : No .
( screams )
( screams and cries )
Beastman : There 's something rotten inside you .
Twisted up .
It secretes bad things .
Stop fighting it . Let it out !
You know you are evil .
No , this is not in the script ! No , no , no !
( screams )
( Alice screams )
Charles !
- ( choking ) - ( Alice whimpering )
( exhales )
( cracking )
I am the horror !
( screams )
- Frederick : Cut ! - ( Alice screams )
Frederick : What the fuck is going on ?
Alice : Charles !
- Charles ? - Alice : ( crying ) No !
What are you doing ?
( crew member coughs )
( screams )
- Alice : Frederick ! - No .
( coughs )
What ? W ... Why w ...
You did this ! This is all your fault !
( screams
Nina ! Come back !
- Nina ! - ( cries out )
Nina !
No , please , please , please ! Get away from me , please !
It 's all right . It 's all right . It 's me !
It 's me , Enid . All right ? I 'm your sister .
( crying ) You ... You killed Charles .
No . No , he was gonna hurt you .
Alice Lee : ( sobbing ) He was my friend !
No , everything that I have done is to protect you .
All right ? To make things right .
- ( sobbing ) You 're insane . - No ! Please .
( screams ) Please !
- Please don 't hurt me ! - No , it 's all right , it 's all right !
I 'm not gonna hurt you .
Never hurt you .
' Cause you 're my sister .
W ... what ?
That wasn 't real !
Well , it has to be . Please , because .
' Cause you have her eyes .
I already have a sister and it 's not you !
No .
No , please , no . You ...
No , you have to be her , please !
No , please , be her . Please !
Please , be her . Please !
Please , you have to be her ! Please .
( crying ) Please , you have to be her ! Please .
You have to be her , please . ( whimpers )
You have to be her , please .
( sobbing )
Please , you have to be her , please .
Please , you have to be her .
( crying ) Please .
Please .
Please . Please , be her .
Please , be her . Please , please .
Please , be her . Please , be her .
Please , be her .
( video static )
( heavenly music playing )
( gasps softly )
Nina !
You came back to save me .
Yes .
I did .
Come on , let 's go home .
( laughing )
News presenter : And what 's fascinating is ,
that now these issues have been dealt with properly ,
the video nasties have been eradicated completely .
The crime rate in Britain has actually dropped to zero .
It 's just like we said ,
the streets of Britain are safe at last .
The employment rate is at a record high .
The criminals are all locked up .
( Enid laughs )
There 's nothing to be afraid of .
( heavenly music continues )
( laughs )
( mouths ) Found her .
- Save me ! - ( music distorts )
Alice : Help me !
( screams )
( laughs )
- ( video static ) - ( player clicks )
( operatic music plays , man vocalizing )